

MARIE MOORE

FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER

CONTACT



- ✓ marie.rodiet@gmail.com
- 2 77163 MORTCERF
- https://mariemoore.site
- in /in/marie-rodiet-moore

HARD SKILLS

- HTML, CSS, SASS
- JAVASCRIPT, TYPESCRIPT
- REACT, REDUX
- FIGMA, WIREFRAME
- GIT, NPM, SEO
- TESTING, DEBUGGING
- RESPONSIVE APPS
- BOOTSTRAP, TAILWING

LANGUAGES

English $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$

French $\bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet \bullet$

Chinese •••••

SOFT SKILLS

- Organized
- Pragmatic
- Empathetic
- Critical thinking
- Adaptability

PROFILE

I am a self-motivated professional with a strong capacity for finding solutions, something I have learned through more than a decade of international life, first in China, then in the United States. The drive that led me to gain functional or native fluency in Chinese and English has also let me to pursue coding languages with the same passion. Put simply: I love communication and problem-solving in all its forms, whether that means with other people, or as a bridge between people and their technology. I am looking for a work environment that will challenge me in both ways.

EDUCATION

2021-2022 Front-End Web Developement (Bachelor)

OPENCLASSROOMS

React Data Table Component Library

This React Component library was compiled with Vite and fully tested and documented before being published on NPM. It includes: pagination, filtering and sorting of data by clicking on the column header arrow icon. It is very customizable: you can choose to include or remove indexing and title, you can change between the dark or light theme and also have the possibility to select/unselect rows.

Health Wealth

This is a CRA app getting data from a form, storing it globally with Redux and displaying it with my data table package.

2020- Responsive Web Design

2021- JavaScript Algorithms and Data Structures

CERTIFICATS FREECODECAMP

2014-2016 Master Littérature Française

University of Oregon

2007-2010 Licence d'Anglais LCE, Option Chinois

University of Malta, ULCO

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

2017-2020 Administrative Support Specialist, Lane Community College, Eugene OR. USA

2014-2016 French Language Instructor, University of Oregon, Eugene OR. USA

2011-2013 Student in Chinese, Kindergarten and Primary School teacher, Tianjin. CHINA